Sir Ping?
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[SHERYN] Sir Ping?
He went to a mythical place.
Just come back next week.
Wait, wait, wait!
- Me first.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Ah!
Hey, wait!
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[JUNE] Papa Ping!
You look like you need
a drink.
Here. The weather's hot.
Have some juice.
I got you milk tea, sir.
I already have some water.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're right.
It's hot.
[SULTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
[SPITS]
[COUGHS]
Hey! It's not that hot.
You're overreacting.
Put this back on.
What are you doing?
What do you mean,
"What are you doing?"
Are you seriously going
to work dressed like that?
Have you no shame?
That's rich coming from you.
You're even willing to sell
yourself for money.
How many guys have
you fooled?
Hey, hey, hey.
Let me tell you.
I worked for everything
I have.
I pour myself
into work,
so I have no time
to flirt like you.
You two are so noisy.
I can't focus here.
You heard him,
so stop bothering him.
Hey, hey, hey!
- Put this on.
- No!
[WATER SPLASHES]
My stuff!
I'll get it.
I'm here anyway.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Cramp! Help!
Ow!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]